
// // This file contains the quiz questions
// var questions = [

//     {
//         question: "How many teams are in the NBA?",
//         choiceA: "30",
//         choiceB: "32",
//         choiceC: "28",
//         choiceD: "40",
//         answer: 'choiceA',
//     },
        
//     {      
//         question: "Who won the MVP during the 2018-2019 season?",
//         choiceA: "James Harden",
//         choiceB: "Lebron",
//         choiceC: "Kawhi",
//         choiceD: "Giannis",
//         answer: 'choiceD',
//     },

//     {
//         question: "What is the most amount of points scored in a single game by one player?",
//         choiceA: "110",
//         choiceB: "100",
//         choiceC: "81",
//         choiceD: "72",
//         answer: 'choiceB',
//     },

//     {
//         question: "What was the second NBA team that Lebron played for?",
//         choiceA: "Cavaliers",
//         choiceB: "Lakers",
//         choiceC: "Heat",
//         choiceD: "Knicks",
//         answer: 'choiceC',      
//     },

//     {
//         question: "Who was the most recent #1 overall pick?",
//         choiceA: "Ben Simmons",
//         choiceB: "Zion Williamson",
//         choiceC: "Deandre Ayton",
//         choiceD: "Karl-Anthony Towns",
//         answer: 'choiceB',    
//     },

// ];

// // var questions = [{
// //         question: "How many teams are in the NBA?",
// //         choices: ["30", "32", "28", "40"],
// //         answer: "30"
// //     },
        
// //     {      
// //         question: "Who won the MVP during the 2018-2019 season?",
// //         choices: ["James Harden", "LeBron","Kawhi","Giannis"],
// //         answer: "Giannis"
// //     },

// //     {
// //         question: "What is the most amount of points scored in a single game by one player?",
// //         choices: ["110", "100", "81", "72"],
// //         answer: "100"
// //     },

// //     {
// //         question: "What was the second NBA team that Lebron played for?",
// //         choices: ["Cavaliers", "Lakers", "Heat", "Knicks"],
// //         answer: "Heat",      
// //     },

// //     {
// //         question: "Who was the most recent #1 overall pick?",
// //         choices: ["Ben Simmons", "Zion Williamson", "Deandre Ayton", "Karl-Anthony Towns"],
// //         answer: "Zion Williamson "  
// //     },

// // ];
// // export  {questions}